intel.in 2012-06-02

# Intel® Online Privacy Notice Summary

_The full Intel Online Privacy Notice and this summary apply to Intel Corporate web sites worldwide._

## Personal Information

Intel collects personal information for a variety of reasons. For example, to deliver a product or service that you have requested, enable your participation in online activities, or personalize your experience. We will explain why we need to collect this information when we ask you for it and keep it to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations.

## Uses

Intel will use your personal information for the purpose it was collected. We will not use your personal information for a different purpose without first asking your permission. We may share your personal information with Intel Corporation in the US, with any Intel subsidiary worldwide, or with authorized third parties. We do not allow third parties to use your personal information for a different purpose.

## Choices

You may access and update your personal information and communication preferences by using one of the following methods: visit the specific product or service web site; visit the Intel Subscription Center; visit the [Intel Profile Center](https://ssl.intel.com/ipc-app/default.aspx); or contact us using the online form.

## How to Contact Us

You can contact Intel by using the Contact Us form or send a letter to the mailing address listed below. Please include your contact information, name of the Intel web site or service, and a detailed description of your request or privacy concern.

Intel Corporation  
ATTN: Privacy  
M/S RNB4-145  
2200 Mission College Blvd.  
Santa Clara, CA 95054 USA

**Last updated:** January 2009
